[{"answer": "Maybe they came back for Chinese food. Y'know my friend, if she gets a craving, she's probably screamin' at those aliens,", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh yeah? I don't believe you've seen... this", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well, a bunch of people are getting together tomorrow night at some bar for her birthday, but... you don't want to go to... that... no", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What little deal", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "A", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "They're coming in", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No, no... Still doin' the big", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Doesn't think anyone can tell", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "U", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No! No!", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Where you had, uh, wooden teeth", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Alright, so", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, it's a tough thing to talk about... I dunno..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You don't know what it was..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I know what it was..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "So, what was it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What actress does she remind you of", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "my friend?", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah, me too..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You came to see m", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I don't see architecture comin from you..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I never said that I was the architect. Just somethin' else..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh, me too. My cousin had to go back to that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah, and that woman was you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Just what I said, here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "She knows what", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "She knows! Oh, I am", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "She knows the whole stupid thing... my friend and the elevator..", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Well, my friend, I never saw you flirt with anyone before. It was quite the spectacle", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh, bye. Good to see you", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Couldn't agree more", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Good", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Good", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stakeout.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Good", "qsentId": 34}]